It's not right.
Why does the most senior staff have to make the video?
Isn't it funny?
It's already decided.
Why? I want to eat too.
Yes, I'll make it.
Wait a minute. Isn't it funny?
Is it just my voice?
Isn't that weird?
I mean, it's not as if I'm the only one.
Just my voice. Why?
No, no, no.
The fans are happy just to hear your voice.
I think that's enough to make them happy.
Then, can you make it soon?
Yes, snow ice.
What?
Stand up a little more.
A little higher.
Lower.
Uh...
If you're going to say "Mock"...
If you're going to say "moc", why don't you take it?
You're free to take it.
Why?
Out?
It's blurry.
It's shaky.
Don't move me.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Talk to me.
Come on, it's not right.
If you keep talking like that, you're gonna get blurry.
I'd like to show you guys something.
I'd like to show you something.I'd like to show you something.
But today...
I'm going to say something.
Why don't you just stand up like this?
What's the point of having it?
That's right, isn't it?
It's called "Vulgar vision".
Your shoulder's going to start moving that way before you know it.
What are you doing?
He wants me to make that.
Yes, sir.
I'm counting on you.
Please, please, please.
Today...
You know what we've been doing all this time?
It's getting warmer
July is here!
Oh, no.
It's getting warmer now
Oh, what kind of
Conviviality
It's getting tough
That's tough.
I'd like to eat some coquin walleye
And syrups.
Strawberry, Hawaiian blue, melon, lemon
and we have condensed milk, too, so...
Oh, no.
Well, I'm glad to hear that.
It's pretty much an annual event.
Sacatan, ah, ah, is it good? This one.
It looks good.
Have you ever done a mint kibori like this? Here.
No, I have not.
It's a regular thing.It's pretty much a tradition.
Every summer.
Oh, okay.
Please do.
Oh! I miss this feeling!
Fluffy!
A little fluffy.
It's making a lot of noise.
The ice is making a lot of noise.
Zubu, don't you see the members doing that?
Why is the staff doing it?
It's so good. Isn't it funny?
Thank you, we got one!
One done!
Favorite color?
I like pink.
Strawberry!
Strawberry! Okay.
Oh, he came by.
It's okay.
Are you the type of person who eats all the sweets and wants condensed milk?
Ha!
I'll just put half on top.
What year is 2020? Now.
23 years.
It's still going.
Can you do it?
You can do it?
What's that? It's covered.
It's a cover. It's definitely a cover.
Are you the one who runs the camera? No, I don't.
Can you at least take the lid off first?
You can go get them for me, if you want.
Thank you.
I'm really glad we get to eat shaved ice.I'm really glad I can eat shaved ice.
It's not always possible to eat shaved ice.
Why not?
Wait a minute.
Can I put the camera down here?
Put the camera down.
If it floats, it's a strawberry, right?
Yes, that's right.
Oh, I dropped it.
It's okay. It's okay.
So, who's going to wipe it off?
I'll wipe it off.
I love that combination.
Looks good.
We have lemon, too.
Yumi.
It's good.
It's delicious.
Delicious.
The end of the show...
It's the best.
At the end of the day
I'm having a drink.
The staff...
The staff is pointing it out.
I'll make sure to use this one, too.
I'll use it.
I just caught it for a second.
Just for a second.
I'm sure it's just a chair.
What do you mean?
I'm sure you're listening, aren't you?
I'll do it again.I'll take care of it.
It's your job, isn't it?
But Yumi, you love me so much.
Of course I love you.
I don't like it.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I said it twice, but there's something wrong.
It's not normal, it's Shimoho-san.
Or... there's something...
Put something to stand on.
It's noisy.
Put it down.
What's the last thing you want?
Melon.
Syrups don't care what color they are.
Wow! It's so good!
I'll mix the colors a little bit.
Oh, yeah! Mixing?
Only in luxury!
Kawayakana.
Yay!
It's good!
I'll make one for you too, Yumi.
That's hard to do.
Wait a minute.
I'll make one for you too, so give it to me first.
Give it to me first.
You're going to make it for Yumi, aren't you?
Yumi's portion
Bon appétit!
Wolf
Soft and fluffy
Melted
It's spilling all over the place.
That's right.
You didn't put any condensed milk on it.Don't put condensed milk on it
You don't put condensed milk on it.
I'm sure.
You've already eaten most of it.
I know...
Make it tastier.
There's no more ice.
It won't come out at all.
Good night.
Ice.
Good luck with the ice.
Maybe we need Yumi's drawings.
You don't need it! They're changing so much right now.
What flavor do you like?
Strawberry.
But can I take strawberry?
I like lemon.
Lemon...
Lemon and condensed milk.
Is it good?
Condensed milk.
Lemon and condensed milk.
It goes well with lemon and condensed milk, doesn't it?
Thank you very much.
Lemon and condensed milk.
My turn.
For the lemon.
No, that's it.
That's the one you're making now, right?
Lemon and condensed milk.
You don't want condensed milk?
No condensed milk?
Not at first.
Now you're being nice.
Put some in hot water for yourself.Put yours in the hot water.
A pear is a pear.
Hey! Hey!
Yummy!
You gotta be kidding me.
Lemon.
I made it with the beef.
Just one more.
Not one more.
Hey, I'm not making it!
Hey, you're gonna make me a nice, clean slice.
Lemmons.
Lemons.
Idiot.
Or fresh tea.
Nama-tea. Stupid.
Yeah, sure.
Stupid.
What is this shaved ice syrup for?
I'll make Yumi's, too.
I'll make it.
It's not too much
I'll make it plainly
I'll make Yumi's too
Which one do you want, Yumi?
Aaaaah!
I don't know which one I'm going to make.
I'm keeping it.
I used two of them.
Okay, I'll make a recommendation.
Recommendations?
Recommendations.
Lots of lemon.Lots of lemon
Lemons
Lemons. Lemons.
Delicious.
I knew I wanted a blue one.
I'm sure you'd like that.
Does it match?
It's so beautiful.
It's really nice.
But there's something...
It's refreshing.
I don't think he's here.
It's like all green.
But it's still a nice accent.
It's important to have a skin.
It's kind of centered.
It doesn't look right.
It's too relevant.
And he added condensed milk.
This is too much fun.
Condensed milk... it's a luxury.
Wow!
I just want one taste.
What is this flavor?
Delicious.
Yubi's omelette rice.
Omelette rice?
Shaved ice
Shaved ice!
Then let's eat Yubi's shaved ice, too!
From the very beginning, from the very beginning!
Finally!
The real English story from the beginning!From the very beginning, the real English story was projected.
Isn't it terrible?
Try it.
Bon appétit.
It's a labor of love made by all of you.
That's right.
Bon appétit.
Delicious!
Good.
Yum! Yum!
It's still good.
The syrup tastes better with dobbedob!
It's good.
Yes, it is.
I miss it.
I wonder what it tasted like.
In a good way.
What does it taste like?
Well, there's always... syrup on top of everything.
Yes, I do.
I'm happy to do it, but I'll do my best.
I'll do my best.
If I'm late, it's your first shot.
Oh, yeah.
It was your first time, wasn't it? Your first shot.
That's why.
Fresh.
It was good. I'm glad you're in a good mood.
I'm glad you're in a good mood.
If I didn't have so much of this, I wouldn't have stopped.
I would have skipped it the moment I stopped.
What I can tell you is that
Yumi is the most senior member of NMB.
It's the breadth of the contents tower.
Even if I beat you with such easyEven if I beat it with such ease.
Two directions.
He takes it in two directions.
He is a wonderful senior
I'm not afraid of Saka-chan either
I've never met such a nice senior
Finally, a good idea...
Who'll stop nominating me?
You really think you're allowed to do that?
No, it's true.
Yes, yes, yes...
That's right.
I'd like to be Yumi's nominee.
Mm-hmm.
Thank you.
That's awesome. You're gonna have to handle it a little more.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Well, then, your highness.
Last but not least, Sakata.
Sakata.
The third and final one.
Tighten it up.
A word of summer.
What's that?
A word of freshness.
Speaking of refreshing, it's high in Sakata.
I'm no good.
I say, "Sawayaka",
A big word for quiet.
Finally, a word of crime.
Two words.
Thank you.
Yumi.Yumi.
Excuse me.
Nice Sakata.
Yumi-san.
Bye-bye.